<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Circle to Share</string>

    <string name="setup_intro">Grab the screen from anywhere, crop it, and share it — without saving anything to your device.</string>

    <string name="setup_step1_title">1. Set as your assistant</string>
    <string name="setup_step1_body">Choose Circle to Share as the digital assistant app (Default digital assistant app → Circle to Share). This makes the assistant gesture — press and hold the power button, or swipe up from a bottom corner — open the crop overlay. If a \"Use screenshot\" toggle is shown there, enable it.</string>
    <string name="status_assistant_on">✓ Active as assistant</string>
    <string name="status_assistant_off">✗ Not set as assistant yet</string>
    <string name="btn_assistant_settings">Open assistant settings</string>

    <string name="setup_step2_title">2. Enable the capture fallback (recommended)</string>
    <string name="setup_step2_body">If your device doesn\'t hand screenshots to third-party assistants, the accessibility service captures the screen instead. Under Accessibility → Circle to Share, turn on the main \"Use\" toggle. (This also powers the floating button below.)</string>
    <string name="status_fallback_on">✓ Fallback enabled</string>
    <string name="status_fallback_off">✗ Fallback disabled</string>
    <string name="btn_accessibility_settings">Open accessibility settings</string>

    <string name="setup_step3_title">3. Try it</string>
    <string name="setup_step3_body">Invoke your assistant (hold the power button, or swipe up from a bottom corner), circle what you want, then hit Share. Tip: the test button below captures this screen.</string>
    <string name="btn_test">Test capture</string>

    <string name="triggers_title">How to open it</string>
    <string name="triggers_body">Ways to trigger a capture — use any of them:\n\n• Power button: press and hold (works via the assistant role from step 1). Set under System → Gestures → Press &amp; hold power button → Digital assistant, if it opens the power menu instead.\n\n• Corner swipe: swipe up from a bottom corner — another way to invoke the assistant from step 1, if enabled in your system settings.\n\n• Floating button (below): the app\'s own always-on-screen bubble you can tap from any app. Drag it anywhere; it stays out of the way. Needs the accessibility fallback (step 2) enabled.</string>
    <string name="switch_bubble">Show floating capture button</string>
    <string name="switch_bubble_note">A small draggable bubble on screen. Tap it to capture, crop, and share from anywhere.</string>
    <string name="error_bubble_needs_accessibility">Enable the accessibility fallback (step 2) first — the bubble runs on it.</string>

    <string name="crop_hint">Drag to crop — or share the full screen</string>
    <string name="crop_hint_freeform">Circle what you want — or share the full screen</string>
    <string name="switch_freeform">Circle to crop</string>
    <string name="switch_freeform_note">Draw a freeform loop around what you want and its outline becomes the crop box. Turn off to drag a rectangle directly.</string>
    <string name="action_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="action_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="action_share_full">Share full</string>
    <string name="share_title">Share screenshot</string>
    <string name="copied">Copied to clipboard</string>

    <string name="error_no_capture">Couldn\'t get a screenshot. Enable the fallback in the Circle to Share app, or turn on \"Use screenshot\" in assistant settings.</string>
    <string name="error_capture_failed">Screen capture failed (secure screen?)</string>
    <string name="error_not_assistant">Set Circle to Share as your assistant app first.</string>
    <string name="error_no_settings">Couldn\'t open settings on this device.</string>

    <string name="accessibility_service_label">Circle to Share</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">Lets Circle to Share capture the screen when you trigger it — with the assistant gesture or the app\'s floating button — so you can crop and share it. Nothing is captured until you trigger it, and nothing is saved to your device.</string>
</resources>
